gaaiho.com 2018-09-30

# Gaaiho PDF│Expertly Create, Edit, Secure and Annotate PDF - Privacy Statement

ZEON Corporation and its subsidiaries ("ZEON") provides this Privacy Statement ( "Privacy Statement ") to help you understand how we collect, use and disclose information, including personal information that you may provide to us or that we may obtain as our products and services are used. We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time and you are advised to check for updates from time to time. This Privacy Statement applies to www.gaaiho.com ("Website") and to certain Gaaiho products, and services, including those for consumer use ("Products"). "Personal Information" includes information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you or a specific individual.

  *     * ZEON may gather and process information about you, including (but not limited to) information in the following categories: 
      * Personal Information (e.g. name, address, telephone, email address);
      * Electronic identification data (e.g. IP addresses, cookies);
      * Banking and payment information (credit card information, account number);
      * Products or services ordered and delivered;
      * Your user profile;
    * The purpose for which we collect Personal Information is to assist us in providing you with the products and services you have requested. Unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Statement, we will not use your Personal Information for any purpose which is not related to the products or services you have requested or for any purpose which you would not reasonably expect us to use the information. We typically use your Personal Information for the following purposes: 
      * Our Site may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by anyone who has access to them. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, please contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

      * If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain Personal Information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

      * ZEON may allow customers to register products online or through similar ways. Personal Information or data provided for such purposes may be used to carry out the request, service, or agreement for which the information is submitted. Under your consent, we may also use the information provided in online registration forms to notify you about new ZEON products and services, and special offers and promotions in which you might be interested.

      * Based upon the Personal Information you provide to us, we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the Services requested, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

  * Except as provided below, ZEON shall not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any personal and/or traffic data or communications content to any third party without your explicit permission, unless it is obliged to do so under applicable laws or by order of the competent authorities.

ZEON may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, to protect Gaaiho and ZEONs interests, to enforce our policies or to protect anyones rights, property, or safety.

ZEON may share your information with ZEONs subsidiaries for purposes of (1) data storage or storage; (2) providing you with access to our websites and applications; (3) guiding decisions about websites, applications and communications; (4) for other purposes described in this privacy statement.

In order to provide you with Gaaiho products you have requested, Gaaiho may sometimes, if necessary, share your personal and traffic data with carriers, partner service providers and/or agents, for example the distributors of Gaaiho software and/or Gaaiho products, and/or the third party banking organizations or other providers of payment, email delivery, analytical services, customer support, or hosting services. ZEON will always require these third parties to take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data and traffic data and to observe the relevant legislation.

Some Gaaiho products may be co-branded and offered together with or via a partner company. If you register for or use such products, you consent to both Gaaiho and the partner companys use of personal data collected in connection with the co-branded product.

ZEON, ZEONs local partner, or the operator or company facilitating your communication may provide personal data, communications content and/or traffic data to an appropriate authority lawfully requesting such information. Gaaiho will provide all reasonable assistance and information to fulfil this request and you hereby consent to such disclosure.

  * Cookies are pieces of information that the Gaaiho software may store on your computer's hard drive in order to help web applications to recognize you or your preferences. Website's cookies may contain identifying information. Cookies enable ZEON to gain information about the use of its websites. This information may be analyzed by third parties on our behalf.

    *       * Security: These cookies allow ZEON to secure access to your account
      * Preference: These cookies are used to store your preferences such as language
      * Analytics: We track site traffic patterns so we can identify popular site content and potential site problems
      * Third Party Cookies: The ads appearing on our websites are delivered to you by our web advertising partners. Please be aware that these third parties may use cookies to obtain information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information) .This information is used to serve ads to you.
    * Gaaiho web pages may include clear gifs. Clear gifs (also known as web-beacons) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, which are used to count your visits to the page (but which do not retain any personally identifiable information). In addition, Gaaiho uses clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened and acted upon. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being set, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings, which vary from browser to browser. Therefore, we advise to look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you clear your cookies, you will need to opt out again. If you use a different computer or browser, your choices will not be carried over.

  * Gaaiho website may contain links that will let you leave Website and access another website. Linked websites are not under the control of ZEON and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. The Privacy Statement applies solely to personal information that is acquired on the websites or through your use of the Gaaiho software, Gaaiho products and/or your relationship with Gaaiho, so ZEON urges you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. ZEON accepts no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

If you use any extras, plug-ins or third party applications together with the Gaaiho software ("Applications"), the provider of such Applications may obtain access to certain personal information about you. ZEON does not and cannot control how the provider of Applications may use any personal information acquired in connection with such Applications. Please ensure that you review any privacy policies or other terms applicable to the use of such Application before installation.

  * ZEON shall take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the personal data and traffic data provided to it or collected by it with due observance of the applicable obligations and exceptions under the relevant legislation. Your personal and traffic data can only be accessed by authorized employees or consultants of Gaaiho or the concerned ZEON Group entities that need to have access to this data in order to be able to fulfill their given duties. However, despite our efforts, no security controls are 100% effective, and we cannot completely ensure or warrant the security of your personal information.

ZEON will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: (1) fulfill any of the Purposes (as defined in article 1 of this Privacy Statement) or (2) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts.

  * Gaaiho reserves the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Statement if deemed necessary. We will inform you of these changes by publishing the revised Privacy Statement on this Website. You should periodically check www.gaaiho.com, our other websites and this privacy statement for updates. Your continued use of our applications and websites constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement.

  * You have the right to access and, where relevant, to amend your personal information. Some of your information may be viewed or edited online by logging into your My Account page on www.gaaiho.com. We will respond to requests to view, correct, complete or remove your personal information within a reasonable period of time and upon verification of your identity. ZEON will use its best endeavours to accommodate requests to delete personal information unless it is required to be retained by law or for lawful business purposes.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [support@gaaiho.com](mailto:support@gaaiho.com) with the subject “unsubscribe”.

  * ZEON may transfer your Personal Information within our global operations to fulfill our obligations to you, but subject to the limitations of applicable data protection law and this Privacy Policy. By using the Website or Services, you agree that the applicable laws in Taiwan (R.O.C.) will govern the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications.

  * If you have privacy questions, concerns or complaints you can contact us by the methods below.

In any correspondence, please include the name of the website or application about which you are contacting us: 

    * By postal mail: 

Zeon Corporation  
3F., No.37, Dexing W. Rd., Shilin Dist., Taipei City 11158, Taiwan (R.O.C.)  
Attention: Privacy

    * By email: 

Last updated: April 15, 2015
